dyson360eye.com 2019-06-25

# Homepage

“Dyson engineers are focused on making hardware and software work together to develop high performing technology which understands the environment it is in and how to improve it. Our machines are increasingly intelligent, but with knowledge comes great responsibility. We are deliberately lean with the data we capture and handle it with great respect. We treat as a priority the protection of your privacy and the protection and secure storage of your data.” 

Sir James Dyson 

At Dyson we’re committed to ensuring that your personal information is protected and never misused. To make better technology and experiences, we collect information through Dyson websites, the Dyson Link app and through our connected machines. We protect that information carefully and handle it with discretion. We’re open about its use and will always make you aware of the information you’re sharing. For your peace of mind, we have explained precisely what information we collect, why we collect it, how we protect it, and the controls you have to change it or delete it. Your trust is important to us. And as our technology becomes more advanced, we’ll continue to put your privacy first. 

##  Our Privacy Principles 

Your privacy is engineered into everything we do.  Privacy policies can be complicated. We've tried to make ours as clear as possible and summarised how Dyson handles your personal information in our privacy principles below. 

### Giving you control

We give you control over the personal information we hold about you to ensure it is accurate and reflects your preferences.

### Open & Honest

We are fair and transparent about how we use the personal information we hold.

### We'll never sell your data

We will never sell your personal information and only share it as outlined in our privacy policy or when you ask us to.

### Dyson's responsibility to you

We take responsibility for the personal information that we hold about you.

##  Examples of how we collect your personal information and how we use it: 

### Your name

To identify you and provide personalised customer service.

### Your phone number

To contact you about your delivery.

### Your email

To communicate with you about your orders, your Dyson products and our latest offers.

### Your Dyson product serial numbers

To assist you if anything goes wrong, honour your warranty and help you find new accessories.

### Your addresses

To deliver your products and verify your payment details.

### Your payment details

To process your secure payments to us.

### Cookies

To enhance your experience on our website and help improve it. Cookies are also essential for online shopping allowing you to put items in the basket for example.
